Hey,
hey, hey.
Hey.
Hey. Hey.
All right, y'all. We are live.
live. We are live
on this beautiful Friday. God bless
everybody in the name of Jesus, Yeshua,
the Messiah. I I pray you and your
families are super blessed as we are
shorting Bitcoin to zero right now. I've
had enough of this. I've had enough of
this. No volatility, man. That's it. My
target is zero. I've I've I've sold
everything.
We got to give a big shout out to
everybody in the chat.
Let's see who we got in the chat. Big
shout out to Juan Estrada. God bless
you, bro. Shout out to Billy Bong. He
says Jason Caf casher. Casher.
Look, I don't use cash at all. I only
use crypto. Crypto. That's the way to
go. Shout out to Sea Train. Shout out to
Darren 982. Shout out to Death Witch
Gaming YouTube who says late. Yeah, I'm
a little late, man. I'm a little late.
Look, I I had a lot of work to do out in
the yard. And all of a sudden, it was
1:14 and I'm like, my goodness, I was
supposed to schedule a stream for 100
p.m. today. What was I thinking? So, I
had to rush in.
Better late than never, they always say.
Howdy. Anyone seeing MSTR price action
today? Crazy. We're going to be checking
that out for sure.
Shout out to R Pink, my man.
Shout out to Matt the WHKB. Been a
while. What up, Jay? What up, bro? Good
to see you, man. Shout out to Rod
Schultz. Shout out to Idk It 6804. I bit
600 million into Bitcoin in 3 days.
Interesting. Shout out to Smith Grind.
And shout out to Daniel CA Prude. 300
days in the bear. That means we have 65
days left until the bull baby dump. Yes,
dumping hard. Nah, I wish. Alts are
about to crash, says Juan. Shout out to
Ronan Mutum.
Rontan Mutum. I'm doing pretty good. How
are you doing? All right. Shout out to
Bon Voyage and ESKR with the chicken.
What's up, everybody? Shout out to
CryptoClown World, guys. Make sure to
smash the dang like button. All right,
cuz we're trying to get we're trying to
get 10,000 likes in the first half hour.
If we get 10,000 likes in the first half
hour,
I can't say it cuz you guys will someone
will will bot the stream and we'll do
it. I was going to say we'll give away a
whole Bitcoin, but nah nah nah. So,
let's see what is going on here, guys.
You know, the long trade from the Casper
crew is still wide open
over on Bitbase. The short trade that
I've been in all week is still open over
on Antarctic and it was up $1,000, but
it's currently up right now 370.
And really, we're going to be discussing
what is likely to happen with this
Bitcoin price action. We're going to be
taking a look at some other assets as
well as Bitcoin right now, guys. I mean,
you can see you can see the importance
of what's happening right now on the
chart. We are coming up and smacking
into value area high. All right, I would
say this on the daily candles, we have a
breakout, close, back test, um, and hold
above this green trend line. The daily
still looking bullish. The 2-day still
looking bullish. The 3-day,
we are printing a green dot, which will
confirm in 6 hours and 18 minutes. And I
do still have to say, guys, so long as
we're holding above $64,000,
I think we could see the squeeze up to
67 or potentially
74 US Donald Trump's. I still have to
hold to the same biases I've had
literally all week, guys. You know, just
it kind of is what it is. It kind of is
what it is. Shout out to Larry Garcia.
Shout out to the Gamer X. Shout out to
Gravy Train. Shout out to Governor Fool
who says word up. Shout out to two real
for you.
Um, we got a head and shoulders says
Ronan Mun.
You know what? I'm just going to go
based on the the old market structure
here, which is this.
So long as we're holding above the back
test of this trend line,
I don't see why we can't get more
movement to the upside considering the
high time frame signals. All right, but
we're going to do some top down analysis
here on Bitcoin as we are heading into
the end of the week.
All right, as we are heading into the
end of the week, we're going to hold
646. That would be bullish. That would
be bullish. Shout out to Wong Steven
8381. What is going on, bro? Guys, you
know what's so crazy? You know what's so
crazy? I'm officially
36 years old. I'm 36 years old right
now. Isn't that crazy? Isn't that crazy?
Who would ever thought, you know, when I
was 26 years old, 36 years old seems so
far away, so far. But I'm closer right
now to 50 than I am to 20. I'm closer to
50 than I am to 20. My goodness. And I
might as well just be 70. If you're 50,
you might as well be 70, honestly. Cuz
when you're 50, you're closer to 70 than
20. And when I'm 70, I might as well be
90. I'm I'm 90. I'm 90 years old, guys.
Can you believe that I'm 90 years old?
Who would have thought at 90 I'd be
walking on a treadmill with a weighted
vest? You know what I'm saying?
How much money do I have? I don't think
I want to disclose that information here
on the internet, man.
I'm broke. Okay, I literally have
nothing. Okay, I have nothing.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah, I I have nothing. I'm I'm I lost
it all, man.
Um
yeah, that's crazy. That is crazy. That
is crazy. That is crazy. That is crazy.
That is crazy. That is crazy. Okay,
let's pop right into the Bitcoin price
action, man. We're going to start on our
weekly time frame since it is a new
week. And I just want to take a quick
look at market cipher B. Now remember
earlier this week guys, Market Cipher B
was printing a red dot here. That red
dot has since faded and we still have a
bullish divergent
right here.
Right here
boom.
Isn't that crazy? Now we have not seen a
bullish divergence on market cyb again
since November 2022. The last time we
saw a bullish div on the weekly was
right down here. Okay, so this is a
historic signal on Bitcoin. And as we go
to the daily time frame, again, we saw a
very bullish looking bottom right here.
Divergence getting higher. We have
multiple Bit Boy green dots down here.
All right, these are these signify that
a significant bottom is in. When you
have two in a row followed by another
one with a divergence, that's a pretty
powerful bottom signal. I don't I can't
even remember the last time we had
something like that,
you know? Did we even have that in
November?
You know, we didn't even have that in
November, guys. Very interesting. So,
this also might be a historic signal
right here on the daily time frame. And
after we got the divergence, the money
flow is crossing to the upside. We have
a confirmed trigger wave. We go to our
2-day. We also have a confirmed trigger
wave here. It confirmed yesterday. On
our 3-day, in 6 hours, we will confirm a
trigger wave after a bullish divergence
with the money flow getting higher. Nice
tight on the zero line. very interesting
historic signals. Okay, now you
interpret them as you will, but they are
bullish nonetheless. Look at the 12-h
hour here. I, you know, the money flow
on the 12 hour. As we made that bottom,
the money flow is getting higher. The
money flow continues to get thicker here
on the 12-h hour and we have a beautiful
bullish divergence followed by beautiful
trigger wave continuation.
All right. So, all these things on these
high time frames do look like we
definitely have the potential for the
rest of August to see some upside. And
honestly, I would not be surprised to
see I mean, my my first target is going
to be 60 $68,000.
Essentially, my first target would be
coming up to here. Let's clear away this
for a second here.
basically coming up to around the high
volume node of this previous range up
here,
right? Coming up to the highs of this
and then maybe getting a bit of a
reversal and continuing to range in here
for a bit. The second target is going to
have to be the $74,000 level. And the
reason for that is because if we look at
all the volume here, well, that's the
value area high of the range. And also
if we pull the Fibonacci golden pocket
from the high to the low
scoop, I mean it lines up perfectly. The
resemblance is striking,
right? So So technically I I would say
as long as we're holding above this high
volume node here, $64,000. As long as
we're holding this, I'd say the highest
probability is a move to the upside here
based on the high time frame uh bullish
signals here. [music] Now, as we go come
lower, this is where things start to
look a little bit different. Obviously,
the 4hour time frame right now is about
to print a bearish divergence,
right? As the price is getting higher
into the value area high of the range,
we do have the dreaded upside down
uneven butt cheek pattern coming on in
with the big juicy fat thick on the
left, skinny on the right. In fact, if
we superimpose it onto the Oh, we can't
superimpose anymore. I forgot how to do
that. My computer doesn't do that
anymore. Um, Bit Boy Green Dots.
Remember the weak face gave him Marcus
Cipher. Bit Boy went all in every time.
Yeah, I remember that. I remember that.
That's why I started my YouTube channel.
I started my YouTube channel because
[laughter] a Bit Boy. I'm not even
kidding.
Hey yo, I'm a pirate, baby. Ohoy, look
out here. I'm [music] eating chips.
Ohoy. All day I'm just out here. A
sloppy [singing] dirty boy. J. Casper.
Man, hopefully I'm not annoying, but I
[music] got to tell a story. Hopefully,
baby, my story is not too boring.
Reminds me of the day that I started my
channel. [music] I was wearing some
jeans and a nice red flannel. I was
driving home back to my house. I turned
[music] on the YouTube looking for a
mouse thinking about when I could sit on
my couch. [music]
Jake Casper, man, he was such a slouch.
But I saw a video [music] boy channel.
He said, "I got an indicator. Can you
handle? Can you handle? Can you sniff my
sandals? He was talking about the
massive green candle. He had a new
[music] indicator called market cipher.
He was so excited. He was so hyper. He
said, "This will make you [music]
profits real quick. Just long every
single green dot, you slick." He said,
"Just [music] long the green dot and
you'll get paid." So, I did it anyway.
Turns out I got liquidated. I couldn't
make [music] any money. Hey, so I
decided to make some videos getting
excited to teach people how to use
Market Cipher himself cuz obviously Bit
Boy couldn't help. So Jay Casper [music]
came out with the 244. The best
strategy, baby, right out the door. You
got to wait for the [music] green dot on
the 4 hour, then the 24 minute pops. We
got the power. Boom. We go straight up.
Massive green candles like the coffee in
the cup. Then everybody [music] liked
the dang video. So I made another and
another and the next thing you know,
Crypto [music] Face, he had me on his
channel and Bit Boy too in a flannel.
They said I was an expert. Then my
[music] subscribers grew like a squirt
of water from the gun. Super sober
blasted off. It's the one. You got to
pump all the air into the tank. Fake
caster making videos, baby. Make it
bank. off. And [music] once I saw that I
had all subscribers, I was looking like
a v viber. I had the glasses. I had the
plunger. Jay Casper on the treadmill
[music] going under.
Yeah, that's that's the story of my
YouTube channel, man.
That's the story of my YouTube channel
in musical form.
Bit Boy made that video saying long the
green dots and I realized, you know
what? there's literally no good market
cipher tutorials out there. Let me go
ahead and make some videos on it. That's
what I did, man. And then after a while,
Cryptoface had me on his channel.
Cryptoface hooked me up with Bit Boy. I
got on Bit Boy's channel. Bit Boy said,
"This guy's a this guy's a trading
expert."
I mean, I don't know. All right, I ran
with it. Right. Then all of a sudden I
have 55,000 subscribers
and I'm out here longing the the 4 hour
24 strategy and all this kind of good
stuff. Man, those were the days, baby.
Um,
those were the days, baby. Man, I miss
those days. I miss those days, guys.
That was six [music] That was six years
ago already now. Basically, that was six
years ago.
My goodness.
Sheesh. All right. So, yeah, let's get
back to the uh the Bitcoin chart here.
But here's the thing. Yeah, we we're
potentially printing a 4 hour bear div.
Money flow is still looking okay. Here's
where it starts to get a little
concerning. The 1 hour time frame,
right? The money flow is coming down on
the 1 hour,
right? We got ourselves this
bearish divergence, the money flow
coming out. The the 1 hour looks kind of
bad. So, here's what I would say. Again,
this leads me back to my same
conclusion. And as long as we can hold
above 64K, we're looking good. Cuz
here's the thing right now. Right here.
You guys see what this is here? Do you
guys see what I see here? Do you see
what I see right here? Here. Let's Let's
clean off everything. Look at this right
here, guys. Look at this. This is a
perfect double bottom.
My goodness. Ah, I guess it's not the
most. We did get a CDW. H. Okay, never
mind. It's not the best looking double
bottom,
but you know what?
I would say this man, we are setting
ourselves up for something like this.
All right, a weekend dump. We come down.
If we get something like this, guys. All
right, where the price comes down to
make a lower low like this and back test
this trend line. All right, that will
give us a very bullish looking uneven
uneven. You know, you know what I'm
saying? Price comes down, market cipher
gets higher. [music] Boom. That could
give us a nice uneven. So this bear div
could turn bull. All right, we have been
squeezing and consolidating all this
time. All right, the long trade given in
the moment in the Casper Crew VIP
Discord during the Wednesday live stream
is still up right now at like $8,000
about. All right, $8,000 still. The
trade given in the Casper crew, the
swing long from the 25th of June is
currently up over 43K. All right. So,
all in all, $50,000 from the setups
given in the Casper Crew VIP Discord at
jasonaspertrading.com.
Again, you can sign up for the paid
group. Cuz remember, I'm broke and I
have no money. So, I need you please to
sign up. But look, if you don't have any
money and you don't want to sign up,
here's what I recommend. [music] All
right? I recommend you go to Jason
Casper's YouTube channel. All right? You
go to playlists and you go to the free
course. This one here, 18 sessions for
free. This will this will give you all
the juice. Then you don't even need to
join the dang VIP Discord cuz really the
VIP Discord. I'm just telling you what
you know the stuff that I would teach
you in this in this course anyway. It's
totally free. All right. So, it's a good
deal. Check it out. [music] Check it out
and try it. Try it and check it. Check
it and try it. Try it and check it. Take
some freestyle rap ideas from the chat.
Man, I ain't no Harry Mack, bro. I ain't
no Harry M. You know, [music] around the
blockchain. I miss around the
blockchain.
I do miss around the blockchain.
It's been 3 years since Bit Boy went off
the deep end. [music]
Yeah. Yeah. That's That is crazy. When
was that? 2023.
Is that 2023? Sheesh.
Yeah, man. And I I pray for Ben. I
legitimately pray for him all the time.
Whenever I think about him, I say a
prayer for him because
that's a sad situation, man. That's a
real sad situation.
But
but hey, it is what it is, I guess. Uh
Enjoy says it's an amazing free course.
I rewatched those this morning to
freshen up. Nice, man. Yeah. Also, also
in addition to this free course, I have
a half done free course over here called
day trading full guide. All right, this
one I get naked in tropical paradise to
teach you how to trade. All right, so
who wouldn't want that? And also this
has how many sessions here? 1 2 3 4 5 6
7 eight sessions. So all in all 18 plus
eight, what's that? 26
26 free sessions. And not only that, if
you also go to playlist and just go to
the trading strategy playlist, [music]
uh where is it? Crypto trading
strategies, guys. I mean, in general,
like look at all the all these videos
here. I have 49 videos of just different
trading strategies is totally free.
Check it out. I mean, seriously, I'm not
even kidding. Like, the amount of
information I put out for free over the
years is ridiculous, man. It is kind of
ridiculous, but hey, it's all good. How
to make money in a bare market. Classic.
Scalping Bitcoin like a ninja. Classic.
I short at the exact top. How to find
juicy entries. Classic. Classic.
Classic. Look. Old school Jason Casper.
Wow. Look what a baby I was. You could
tell I was a young baby back then.
Sheesh. This is before I had these
battle scars from the treadmill and the
weighted vest. Man, look at that juicy
shorts right though. Um,
all right. So, yeah. So, here we're
we're back to the chart. Look, as long
as we're holding 64K, I don't see why we
can't continue to squeeze up to 67 and
then potentially 72ish.
All right, let's check out our 24-minut
time frame right now.
24m minute doesn't look so bad on the
momentum waves. Money flow looks pretty
garbageio, but if we do come and make a
lower low, we would also have some nice
bullish divergence here. So
yeah, I'm not too freaked out to be
honest. I was I was honestly more
freaked out when I started the stream
after looking at the chart. I'm not so
freaked out anymore, you know. Big shout
out to my man Juan Estrada. He says that
free course is worth every penny. Yes,
it is, bro. It is worth every penny.
Look, nobody who has ever bought the
free course has regretted spending that
money. All right. I have had zero people
ask for a refund. Zero people ask for a
refund. God bless you, bro. Thank you so
much for uh the super chat, my man. God
bless you. Shout out to Kkumar. Can you
see ETH? Yeah. Let's take a look at ETH,
man. Also, thank you so much for the
super chat. A cocaine gambler. I think
some people do think I'm on cocaine. I
mean, I have a lot of energy. I do have
a lot of energy. I can understand it.
But here's the thing. I've cracked the
code. I know how to have lots of energy
these days. You know, that's the one
thing I like about being 36 more than I
like about being 26 [music] is I know
how to feel good. When I was 26, I
didn't know how to feel well. I didn't
know how to take care of the vessel that
God gave me. I I didn't know. Now that
I'm 36, I I feel way better than when I
was 26. Like way better, you know? So,
that's the one good thing about getting
old is you feel better if you've like
learned how to take care of your body.
If you don't learn, then I guess most
people feel worse. But all glory to the
Lord because you know every breath I
take, every heartbeat is just because of
his mercy and grace. But
but also, you know, taking taking care
of yourself and being a good steward
that's that's that's going to pay off in
dividends. It's a dividend paying stock
right there. Um so here's the deal with
Ethereum. Okay, we are about to actually
let's see here. This is the buy chart.
Let's go to let's go to the Coinbase
chart, you know.
Okay, so the last time we printed a
green dot on the monthly, it was the
bottom. And so obviously we're coming to
a significant bottom here on ETH
um within the next few months or weeks.
Let's go to the twoe time frame here.
Um,
so again, we are seeing bottomness,
not as nice as it was last bare market
bottom, but I say what really catches my
eye on ETH is the weekly bullish
divergence. This actually is historic.
[music] We've never seen a weekly
bullish divergence before on ETH. Never.
Never. And what else is interesting
about this weekly bull div is we we are
down toward the bottom of the range
here. And currently we're trading above
the PC. All right. So if Bitcoin is
going to continue up to $67,000,
well that will keep ETH above this PC.
If Bitcoin goes to 74, we could see ETH
come up to 2500.
Now if ETH comes up to 2500, that is a
major change in the bare market [music]
trend, right? If Ethereum comes up to
$2,500 for the first time since August,
we are making a higher high, right? We
had our our swing high top. We had our
swing high, lower high, our swing high,
lower high. [music]
And so if we come up above this previous
lower high, that is officially now a
change in structure, which means
this is much more likely the the low,
much more likely the lower, right? So,
if this happens, I would be looking for
one of two things. Number one, obviously
a higher low
to come back up toward the high of the
range. What I would most prefer,
obviously, what everyone should always
prefer cuz it just gives you a better
entry would be a double bottom. Not
saying we're going to get that, but in a
perfect world, what we would want to see
is ETH make a higher high and then come
back and actually do tap into the value
area low, which we front ran this time,
right? Right? And we make that double
bottom. If we do something like this, a
higher high followed [music] by a double
bottom, beautiful, beautiful, perfect,
like amazing buy signal entry. I mean,
you you can't ask for anything better
than that. That's why it's so dang
textbook. The other situation would be a
higher low. And in the instance of a
higher low, the way you would set up
that is you'd pull a Fibonacci from the
low to wherever we uh come up to. And
you basically as soon as we come to back
test the PC golden pocket, you kind of
have to go in with your stop loss below
that first low, right? This is kind of
how you would have to play that on ETH,
which gives you a good risk-to-reward
ratio. But basically, you'd have to kind
of look at this PC zone here and see,
all right, are we bouncing from here?
Right? This is a trade you need to take
based on the reaction that we get from
that level. Right? And if we're on a
high time frame, we give it some time.
It's the weekly. But let's say we come
up here, right? We come down. We got a
weekly candle here. And then the weekly
candle closes up here, right? You can
clearly see the bounce happening. That
is basically how you would get your your
entry. And you could take it two ways.
You could say, well, I'm going to go for
this setup here, assuming that this is a
higher low. Or you could say, you know
what, to be safe, the true invalidation
is if we make a lower low,
right? I'm more the type of guy that
will do this and then if it turns out
that this is just a fake out and we do
do this, then yeah, I'll take my dang
loss and then I'll I'll get in again
down here. You know, that's the way I
like to trade. I'd rather take more
trades with a better risk-to-reward
ratio than fewer trades with a worse
risk-to-reward ratio.
>> [music]
>> Um but yeah, right now as long as we're
holding above this white line of around
17 $1,800,
um I'd say more upside is very probable
cuz we are above major resistance
flipped into support. Now again, I do
believe Bitcoin and ETH are probably
going to move together. So,
you know, um, [music]
better buy on ETH is $1,100.
Yeah, you're right, man. A better buy on
ETH is
uh
anything lower than the value area.
Absolutely. Yeah. Now, again, let's
let's not forget this. Um, my time and
price target for Bitcoin is going to be
November around 40k. I'm sorry, October.
40k Bitcoin around October is my price
and time target. And the way I'm playing
it is I am absolutely dollar cost
averaging into Bitcoin as we are
currently 50% discounted.
Um, and any lower dip we get, I'm going
to be buying. All right. And you could
technically do the same thing for ETH.
Um, I don't know what's going to happen
with ETH this cycle. We we might see
altcoins outperform Bitcoin this cycle
cuz nobody's expecting it. Just like
last cycle, nobody expected altcoins to
do nothing. Um,
maybe we see altcoins take center stage
this time. Who knows? Who knows? Um, all
right. Bonvoyage has watched all the
videos and paid courses. Wow, man. Well,
I hope you find it kind of good.
>> [music]
>> saying dirty [__] as a Jew. So I called
myself a dirty [__] [music] right? But I
couldn't think of anything else that
rhymed. So what do you want me to say,
bro? You know, that's why people always
ask me, why don't I freestyle about
anything serious? Because like I don't
know what's going to come out of my
mouth, man. You know,
I don't know what's going to come out of
my mouth.
Uh, Splash Rock Films
says, "Your birthday is this weekend."
Yeah. Yeah, it's my birthday right now.
You know, I'm on the juice. Of course, I
feel good. I'm not on the juice, man.
That's the thing. That's the thing. I've
cracked the code. I've cracked the code
to feel good. Not on the juice.
You know what? I I feel like I feel like
a lot of people who haven't cracked the
code hop on the dang juice. But the
juice, man. The juice is a trap. You're
trying to hop on the juice.
You're going to get trapped, man. Your
testicles turn off. You can't have
babies. You know, I got the opposite
problem. I can't stop making babies
every time. I I look at my wife and she
gets pregnant. It's crazy. I don't even
know how it happens. Honestly, I don't
know how it happens, you know? I don't
know how it happens. They had to have an
intervention with me. They sat me down.
They gave me the health videos from
sixth grade to teach me about the birds
and the beast cuz like I'm like, I don't
know how this keep I don't know why we
have so many babies, right?
you know, the juice, man. You don't want
to you don't want to hop on that. It'll
thicken your blood, you know, and then
if the grid ever really does go down, if
the supply chain ever does go down, then
what? Then you're then you're then
you're stuck as a 95year-old woman,
you know, man, don't take the juice,
guys. Look, there's there's a better
way. There's a better way. Let's check
out micro strategy here.
You know what? Although technically I am
part Jewish
ethnically,
any religious Jew would would consider
me a dirty [__]
Just so [music] you know,
I have Jesus tattooed on my arm.
That's the most that's the most goyish
thing I could possibly imagine from a
Jewish perspective.
All right. So, this is Micro Strategy,
but I thought I had some TA on here. I
do. [music]
Okay. So, you know what?
Let's see here.
>> [music]
>> Someone said, "Check out Micro Strategy
because the TA is wild." So on the
weekly time frame, all I can say is
this. This big green box here is still
our support resistance flip. Until we
reclaim it, I'm not getting bullish on
this. Yes, we have bullish divs on
market cipher B.
You [music] know, we have bullish divs
on market cipher B.
Um,
so yeah, I look here's the thing. If the
Bitcoin bottoms in, then yeah, maybe
Micro Strategy in. But my hope and
dream, all right, my hope and dream is
that Bitcoin does get another low. And
if so, we see Micro Strategy also get
another low. We see some like Michael
Sailor, they've already been selling.
Let's see if they don't get some super
selling going on. All right, some
supercell, some inel action, involuntary
selling cuz the Bitcoin price is so low.
We want to turn Michael Sailor into an
incel. All right. He's involuntarily
selling to push, you know, when he
starts involuntarily selling Bitcoin,
it's going to push the price of Micro
Strategy down. And look at this.
We have this weekly fair value gap. We
have the golden pocket. And also, let's
check it out. We have ourselves the Ah,
no, that's not what I wanted.
Ah, that's not what I wanted either. Let
me see some
Yeah, look at this. We have the previous
range value area high right here. I
would love to come down there. And also
we have this trend line right here. Man,
can you imagine we just do this [music]
and then bam. Well, I don't know. I
mean, assuming this thing comes back,
you know, if this is the next FTX, I
mean, look, we all assume that this
business model can't fail, right? This
is this is this is the Titanic of of
businesses right here, guys. This is the
Titanic of businesses. Now, the problem
is we don't know who out there is the is
the proverbial JP Morgan
trying to sink the Titanic,
you know, just so that they can get
everyone's money. We don't know.
So,
Michael Sailor selling was the mark of
the bottom. Well, he already kind of has
been bottoming. You know what I'm
saying? Michael Seller, the incel. Yeah.
That's funny. If your bank account is
thick enough, women seem to get pregnant
just from you looking in their
direction.
Well, that is a funny joke in our in our
cultural environment.
That is a funny joke in our cultural
environment.
Uh that's how I know Casper's not even
on test. He keeps having more kids.
Who Who needs testicles?
Honestly, I think Tesc are one of the
best assets a man can have. All right.
Seriously, you know that testosterone
that's that's gonna that's going to give
you the drive. It's going to give you
the energy. It's going to give you the
passion. It's going to give you the
focus. It's going to make you a risk
taker. You know, no risk, no reward. You
know what I'm saying? You have to have a
balance, though. That's another thing.
Like, if you're just natural, right?
Yeah. Yeah, you got your testosterone
that's making you a risk taker, but at
least at least you know if you're
natural, you're going to be going for
the 31's, maybe the 4 ones, maybe the
5:1's. You know what I'm saying? So,
normal natural testosterone levels will
keep you taking trades like this, right?
[music] You hop on test, all right, you
hop on TRT, the the risk, it it starts
to go like this, right? It's just too
much. Can't handle it. Now, you start
taking trades like this. So look, you
got to stay natural, guys, for this
reason only. All right? You could end up
like this. You could end up taking
trades like this versus trades like
this, right? You got to take risk, but
not too much risk.
So yeah, let's zoom in a little bit here
on Micro Strategy.
You know what I do have to say? The the
the 4 hour does look bullish. Uh the
daily dancing on the line here. The
daily I would love to see us come back
down. Daily looks like we could get a
move back down.
This 4hour money flow, I do have to say
it looks nice, but oftentimes what we
see in a downtrend is the money flow we,
you know, we spent a lot of time in in
the purple, a little bit in the blue, a
lot of time in the purple, a little bit
in the blue. Last time we got a money
flow across the 4 hour. It did give us a
good oldfashioned lower high and then we
made a lower low. So maybe something
similar to that. I'm curious to see what
may or may not happen in here. Let's
see. Let's Let's get our music back on.
Golden era hip-hop beats.
This is serious, man. This is a serious
beat right here.
This is a serious beat.
Um,
yeah, I'm not really I'm not really
feeling this this beat to be honest.
Where can you get Casper Crew merch? I
think. Yeah, definitely on the website.
jasonencrading.com
and there's a button here for merch.
The hat. That's That's the only thing I
I use the hat and I use these mugs.
Other than that, that's kind of it. I do
have these sweatshirts and stuff, but
let's be honest, they're cool drawings,
but they're not good for shirts. You
know what I'm saying? They're cool
drawings, but they're not good for
shirts.
Shout out to Crowbar, man. What is going
on?
Um,
can you can I look at the 233 minute?
Yeah, we could look at the 233 minute
on Bitcoin or on strategy. Let's take
out Bitcoin. and the 233. Why not the
322 minute
the 233 minute? Let's see here.
Let's check it out.
What a random time frame, man. It's so
random. Market Cipher is having trouble
loading here.
Interesting.
I don't really know what to think about
the 233 minute here.
You know,
Eddie Merge beats.
Yes. Let's liquidate Casper. Guys, try
and liquidate my trades, please. You
know, shout out to Larry Garcia. No way,
man. I have the same birthday as your
oldest son, and we'll both be having our
fourth child around the same time, and
we're the same age. That's true, Larry
Garcia. That's wild, bro. That is that
is honestly really wild. Larry Garcia,
especially since my uncle's name is
Larry Garcia, you know, it is pretty
crazy.
Um, merge beats. Yeah, let's look. Cuz I
don't really like this beat. I got to be
honest. [music]
See here.
Eddie merge beats. Let's see. I wonder
if these Eddie merge beats will make me
feel something in my in my neffesh.
Let's try it out here.
Oh, here we go. Eddie Merch.
[music]
All right, let's
Okay. Okay. Okay.
All right. Okay. All right. It kind of
I'll have to check it out later. Nothing
really makes me feel anything in my
soul, man.
You know,
I have to feel it in my soul right away.
You know
[music] why the 233 minute? Because it's
different from the standard time frames
most people trade. Shout out to
B. Hershey trades. Hershey trades. Yo,
what's up, Hershey? Is this Hershey? Is
this Hershey?
Oh, it's a fib number. Okay. Hey, it's a
fib number. Yeah, guys, liquidate the
shorts. Please liquidate my short trade.
You know, Juan says it gives him a
little bit of a better view. Let's
liquidate this short trade. All right,
guys. Let's do it. Let's do it. Let's do
it.
You have to feel it in your soul.
Exactly. Splash bars.
That's the guy from Drugs Incorporated.
Wait, what was Drugs?
Was that a movie or a B? Wasn't there a
band called Drugs? Wasn't uh what's the
guy's name from Chiodto's?
Come on. My My scene.
My scene.
Crabcore
Generation. Whoa. Wasn't there a band
called Drugs that Craig Owens had?
When I eat eggs, do I fry them or boil
them? I always boil them. I always boil
them. No, that's the best way, man. Boil
the eggs. [music]
Play guitar today. Maybe I will. I do
have a beautiful Les Paul over there.
Right over there. You guys don't see it.
It's right there [music] behind the Tora
scroll.
I haven't touched it.
There's an indie rock band called War on
Drugs. Interesting. Interesting.
Interesting.
Um,
shout out to Mimi me. Life is but a
dream.
I prefer the 288 minute. Let's try out
the 288 minute.
Let's try out the 288 minute.
Oh, it already exists. That's cool. I've
already been chilling on the 288.
What is 288? Let me see something.
Let me see. 288. I'm going to divide
that by 60 to see exactly how many hours
that is cuz I'm too dumb to figure it
out in my head. Here,
4.8 hours.
The 223 is
3.7 hours.
Interesting.
I'm a big fan of the, you know, the 612
to 24 and all that kind of stuff. When
do I expect 39K? October. And honestly,
[music]
when I shout out to make me a millie,
when I say I expect 39K, I should really
honestly say I hope for 39K. [music]
I hope for 39K.
you know, I can't
I can't say I expect it. I hope for it,
you know. Shout out to uh shout out to
my man on his 20th wedding anniversary.
God bless you, man. I'm going to tell
him that right now. Talk to text like a
true boomer. That's amazing, bro. God
bless you both.
Yeah, I text like a boomer. Talk to
text. [music]
All caps. Spelling errors. No
punctuation.
Talk to text. No punctuation.
It's Hershey. I'm on I'm on I'm with the
family on holiday. That's what's up,
bro. Enjoy it, man.
All right. So, Sioken says, "Gun to my
head. I think bottom is 48K, but I would
love Bitcoin under 40." Yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah. Shout out to delinquent YouTube.
What's going on, bro?
Yeah, guys. I can't believe I'm 36. It
is pretty crazy. I started this channel
as a as a young 30-year-old man. Now I'm
I'm so old. You guys can't see it, but
I'm walking with a cane on this
treadmill,
you know. Whoa. What is this here? Toma.
What is this, bro? What? I don't even
know what language this is. I'm going to
try and Google it.
Looks pretty cool. Wish I could read it.
Looks pretty cool.
Yeah, of course. Spicy noodle. I'm still
I'm still My epic trading plan is still
here. All right.
[music] Uh,
what language is Let's see.
It's Georgian.
It means can you play the music?
Lash Kiruli.
Cool. I don't really know anything about
Georgia, but I didn't know their
language looked like this. This is
pretty cool.
I know Georgia is like one of the oldest
Orthodox Christian traditions
that goes back to like the 4th century
or whatever. That's all I know about
Georgia. I don't know anything else
about Georgia except it's down under
South Carolina. [laughter]
Oh man, I hear everyone down in Georgia
talks like this.
You know what I'm saying?
That's the ancient language of the
Travi. Oh, man. That's so funny. Oh, you
know it's Georgian, too. All right.
Okay. We got some got some people from
Georgia up in here. I'm more of a South
Carolina guy myself. You know what I'm
saying? [music]
You know, it is a it is it is a
beautiful script, by the way. It is
pretty cool.
You know,
it is pretty cool.
Shout out to Nibbles Dribbles. What a
cool YouTube name that is.
36 is a spring chicken. I don't know,
man. It sounds old to me.
I never, you know, it it sound, you
know, it just doesn't sound right to be
36,
you know. I don't feel I don't Well, I
don't feel 36. That's good. Praise God.
Guys, you know what? Give me a second
here. I think I'm going to take off this
weighted vest. You know,
it's been uh [music]
how long we've been streaming for?
Like almost an hour. Yeah, I might take
this thing off.
>> [music]
[music]
>> All
>> [music]
>> right, we're back, baby. We are back.
We're back.
We're back. Are we going to pump or
dump? What is going on, Bitcoin? I mean,
sheesh.
How's the hair? I think it's all right.
Started doing 20 minute walks in the
best in the vest. Feeling great. That's
what's up.
That's what's up. [music]
When you're 48, 36 sounds like a
lifetime ago. I still feel like I'm 18,
says digital asset DJ.
Yeah. Yeah.
I I mean, yeah. I would imagine when I
when I'm 40 when I'm 48, that's going to
be like, sheesh, man. I wish I [music]
was 36. When I'm 36, I wish I was 20 26,
you know?
36, wish you were 26. 26, wish you were
16. [music] Just kidding. I never I
never actually wish I was 16 again. Um,
yeah.
All
right. Shout out to not not quicker.
Georgia is where wine was invented.
Really interesting. I didn't know that.
[music] Sorry for typing in Georgian.
That's okay. You could type in Georgian.
Keep keep it Georgian up up here in the
chat, man.
Am I a Gamecock fan? I never even heard
of that.
You know,
my son just got christened into the
Orthodox church. Shout out to Hershey.
Um
what what Orthodox tradition?
Georgian Orthodox, Greek Orthodox,
Ethiopian Orthodox,
just normal Eastern Orthodox.
What happened to the punk song? still
have it. You know,
it's the big question.
Make me a millie. Gety M9Q wants to know
if you take creatine, bro. Do you take
creatine?
We need to know the answer. All right.
Maybe the secret to the wide last is
just all creatine. Wow. 7 to 10 grams a
day, baby.
Maybe I need to start taking creatine.
you know.
Oh, it's South Carolina team mascot. Oh,
sorry. I didn't know that.
I don't I I don't really know anything
about South Carolina to be honest with
you. I was making a stupid joke.
I'm 57, but I trade like I'm 36. I don't
know what that means, but
um
what an interesting beat this is. I I
don't know how I feel about it. I don't
know how I feel about it. Uh,
yeah, I think this one's better.
This one is better.
Ethereum orthodox. Ethereum orthodox.
The cool thing about the Casper Crew
hats, guys, is that they do have a green
under visor, right? So, you know, you
could see through yourself. It's pretty
cool. You can disappear. Like, if you
need to hide in public, you just go like
this. And here's the thing. If if people
can't see your eyes, that means they
can't see you either.
LC carnitine thermogenic.
Doesn't LC carnitine help with fat
metabolism if I'm not mistaken.
Yeah, sorry. Digital asset DJ. Yeah, I
was joking cuz he said he was from
Georgia, the country. So I said I'm from
South Carolina,
which is right next to Georgia, the
state.
It was a dad joke. Look, I'm a 36-y old
dad. What else can I say?
Um,
I don't have a position on micro
strategy.
[music]
Nope. I only have positions right now on
Bitcoin. I mean, well, [music] I mean,
and when as it comes to my actual like
leverage trading right now, I only have
positions on Bitcoin. [music] I have
spot positions on many different assets,
many different assets, many different
stocks, indexes,
cryptos, but as it pertains to my
leverage trading positions right now, I
only have three trade uh Yeah, I
actually, yes, I only have three trades
open.
I only have three trades open. I have
this short trade, this long [music]
trade, and this long trade here,
you know.
I don't know the average number of miles
I walk during a stream.
I don't know
yet. Georgia, what I hear, see, I don't
know much about Georgia. Zivad Zadori
Vvel. But I do have some friends from
Georgia and they tell me in Georgia
Christians, Jews and Muslims all live
together in perfect peace and harmony
and everyone respects each other. And
you got the Orthodox church and the
synagogue and the mosque all right
across the street from each other and
everyone's got each other's back.
That's what I hear about Georgia.
[music] Sounds like a cool place.
Honestly,
that's what I hear about the country of
Georgia.
Nice. E Eastern Orthodox. Hershey
trades. Hershey trades. Were you Were
you born into the Eastern Orthodox
tradition
or did you become Eastern Orthodox
[music] as an older gentleman?
Can I show my short trade? Sure. Why you
trying to liquidate it? Liquidate it. Go
for it. If you're a market maker,
liquidate the dang short trade. Stop
loss at 655 even. Stop loss will be hit
out for $4,000.
$4,000. Go ahead. Stop me out. Liquidate
[music] me. Liquidate me.
You know,
would I visit South Africa?
Um, no. No.
No.
Nope. If I ever leave the United States,
it will be [music]
to go to Cuba or any or I it will be to
stay around America but go south.
[music] All right. The central South
America region is the only place I'll
ever go if I leave the United States.
All right.
So,
[music]
I wish we had peace and harmony in the
States.
Well, [music] the thing is in general we
do, right? In general we do, but there's
always the outliers
and of course there's the media which
you know
the the media representation of reality
is not average reality out in the
street. you know, you go out, you go out
in public,
and most people get along fine,
you know, uh,
but, you know, you go online, you watch
the TV, and everyone hates each other.
[music]
Now, of course, there's extreme groups,
and there are bad people out there doing
bad things, but in general, most people
are not like that.
You know,
I won't go to Israel. No, I won't. I
will not go to Israel. I will not go to
Israel. When uh when the Lord returns,
I'll go to Israel. [music]
No. Everyone Everyone always says,
"Don't you want to go to Israel?" No, I
I don't really I don't really I'm not a
traveler, guys. You have to understand
Do I know 100,000 Georgians were killed
in Georgia because they were they were
Orthodox? Was that Did the Communists do
that? Who did that? Was that Muslims?
Communists? [snorts]
Was that the communists that did that?
Who did that? I'm curious. And when was
that? I'm curious cuz I'm pretty sure.
When did
How long has Georgia not been communist?
Since like the 80s.
Why not Europe? Why would I never go to
Europe? Because Europe, no offense to my
Europeans up in here, but I feel like
Europe's just
uh it's on its way out, man. I mean, so
is the United States, but Europe's like
30, 40 years ahead in its decline.
So, yeah. I have no desire to go there.
I have no desire to go there.
Yeah, there's a lot more good in the
world, but the hate gets amplified. I I
definitely agree with that. I mean,
and I know times have changed too in
recent decades, but you know, back when
I was a young, back when I was in my
teens and my 20s,
you know, I lived in a I lived in a very
uh diverse area. Everyone everyone got
along, everyone respected each other.
Yeah, it just just is what [music] it
is.
You hope I watch rugby. Oh, by Muslims
in 1226.
Um,
yeah. Well, I'm sure is the I don't
think the environment there is quite
like that now, but yeah.
Decline. Then why would I go to Cuba?
because I love Cuba. I'm from Cuba,
you know.
Yeah. Yeah. Europe. I mean, here's the
thing,
you know, Europe is going to be a
completely Muslim continent very soon.
But look, the thing is it's because
Europe has rejected God and now there's
a spiritual vacuum there and it's going
to be filled
by the God of Islam.
So
that's what happens when a nation
rejects the truth or a country or a
continent or culture rejects the truth.
It's going to be filled with some other
kind of spirituality.
It's just a matter of time.
It's just a matter of time. Is Cuba as
bad as they say? It's depends on where
you go. I mean, it's not I have a lot of
family in Cuba.
It is.
I mean, obviously the quality of life in
Cuba is nowhere near like the US. It's
nowhere near like the US, but like in
all places, [music] it really depends
where you go. There's good there's worse
better and worse places,
you know.
Jungle Boy left the USA. I mean, I love
the USA. I have to be honest. You know,
I love the USA.
I
I I love the USA in a sense that this
this country has a lot of freedoms that
other countries don't have.
Um, and the quality of life here right
now is very good. I mean, it's not
perfect. It's getting worse. It's not
going to last forever, but for right
now, I'm pretty happy to be here. I'm
pretty happy to be here, you know. Um,
I don't know if I'll be happy to be here
in 30 years, but I'm pretty happy to be
here for now.
The Lord separated the waters from above
and below with the firmament.
That's what it says.
Yep. God said, he said,
>> [music]
>> Ben a
me
that's what it says in the Bible
says God said let there be a a raia in
the middle of the waters let it divide
the waters from the waters
And so God made the firmament. He
divided the waters which were above the
rakia and the waters which were below
the raia. And it was so. And it says he
called it heavens. He called it shmayim.
Shmayim. [music] Shmayim in Hebrew.
I mean it comes from the wordim. It has
to do with water. [music] And it's
interesting. The word water itself in
Hebrew is a dual
noun mim implies there's two of them
like a naim eyes or naim ears
raglim [music]
your feet yim your hands like it implies
it comes in a pair shim
could mean the dividing of the water
it's interesting what does it mean
what does it mean
you Well, what do you think that means?
There's a lot of different views on it.
You know,
there's so many different views on what
that means. You got your literal view,
you got your pmic view,
you've got your [music]
allegoric view.
But what do you think, my friend?
the way it is. 89. What do you think
about that?
About that Bible verse, bro.
Go to the Hebrew about the formless and
void description in Genesis 1. It says,
Oh, al to home
to vavu.
What do you have to what what are your
thoughts about toou vavohu travy trades?
What do you think about it?
It means there's no space above us, only
water. That's what the way it is.
Thinks about that Bible verse.
Interesting, man.
Interesting view.
That is an interesting view,
you know. I respect it, bro. I respect
it, man. I respect it, bro.
I respect it, man.
Cardano is finally going to explode.
Let's check it out.
I mean, look, if we reclaim uh 221.5
cents, we could easily get a squeeze up
to 50 cents.
Honestly, we reclaim the green line, we
could come up to 50 cents. I do think
that's true, [music] you know. I do
think that's true.
What do I think about XRP at this level?
Um, let's see.
Well, it's a key support resistance
flip, honestly, and it's the 786. We do
have some slight bullish divergence on
the weekly, but it doesn't look too
good, to be honest with you. I'll be
honest, it doesn't really look too good.
It doesn't really look that great.
Um, I don't see any kind of reaction
here yet. I don't see any kind of change
of market structure. You know, we had an
opportunity to take the lows and change
structure. We didn't. So, for XRP, what
I would want to see is I would want to
wait for some kind of sign of strength
or change of structure cuz the
divergences are iffy. They're iffy.
They're iffy. We got another red dot.
Obviously, the support resistance flip
at 93 cents is important. We do have a
fair value gap that could be filled down
at 62 cents.
So, I would want to wait and see some
kind of change of structure before I hop
in. But look, if you
if you
uh are bullish on XRP, then
I mean technically speaking, it's it is
a dollar. That's that's that's a pretty
good price. I mean, we've seen it we've
seen a dollar for a long time, man. XRP,
let's see from the all-time high. Is
that That's not the all-time high. Is
that the all-time high? It's down 73%.
That's a pretty good deal. Let's see.
XRP.
Uh oh, man. You guys hear this beat?
[music]
Uh uh uh. Yeah, man. [music]
Uh
[music] hey yo, J Casper, take a look at
XRP.
Come to the chart. What do we see?
[music]
It looks like a nice treat. We're coming
down to the percent. 73 to the downside.
Let it ride [music] like a water slide.
Let it glide.
We're going side [music] to side. We hop
in the Lambo to ride. Then we fly. We're
going so high. About to blast the
resistance. We go to the sky. [music] We
got the blue candles pumping in my eyes.
J Casper, are you crying? No, I'm not
crying. I got something in my eye, but I
get passionate. When the price starts
[music] to fly, I get emotional.
Don't you know?
Welcome to the Jason Casper [music]
Show. J Casper, here we are. Blue and
purple candles. A work of art. Got the
gas [music] in my belly. Got a fart.
What's that smell? Was it a shark? Oh
no. Now my underwear is dirty. Can you
guys believe that I'm 36 years old? Back
to her old trick. It's the fold like the
[music] sheep. The mold. You got the
moldy apples. Baby fuzzy and green. Jay
Casper on the charts. Baby trading
machine. [music] I give it to you nice.
I never give it. So sit back and I'mma
teach. You know what I mean? Yeah, XRP.
Listen [music] to me.
We got the scribble.
We call it Ripple. [music]
We call it Ripple. Jake Casper coming
out. He got the scribble on the paper.
Got to write [music] the vector. The XRP
pumping up no better, but it's $1, then
[music] we go to two, then we go to
three. As I'm walking in my new shoes on
the treadmill, we're going uphill. About
to change my name from Jay to Bill. Uh,
that was a good beat, but I don't like
the way the I don't like the way it kept
dropping off like that. You know what I
mean? I don't like the way it kept
dropping off like that. Sheesh, man.
You want the beat? This is a playlist
called um
Hip Hop Beats 90s golden era classics 42
by Reserved
by Reserved.
Um
yeah, for sure. It's this playlist. Uh
Behave.
I don't know what the song name is. You
just got to go to minute 16.
Minute
16. Right. Right in that thing.
You like when I give in-depth
explanations of scripture? Well, then
check out the Bible channel, bro.
Check out the Bible channel.
Billy Casper. [music]
Billy Fapster.
I mean, Billy Casper Bible Channel.
Check it out. All right. Go subscribe to
the Billy Casper Bible channel. I
actually have some videos I need to
upload on on here. All right, but check
it out. I have some videos I need to
upload on there.
Right now, I'm going through the Gospel
according to John
verse by verse.
So, check it out if you're interested.
Yeah, Jason Fafser. I didn't mean to
type that.
Um, all right. Let's see. This is You
know what, guys? I promise crypto is not
going to stay this boring. All right.
Crypto is not going to stay this boring.
It's going to It's going to come back.
It's going to come back. All right.
We're going to have We're going to have
big big bulging streams once again. Big
dreams and bulging streams.
I'm just a guy with big dreams and
bulging streams.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, this is this is this is some
boring stuff. All right. Does anyone
else in the chat have anything
interesting to look at? Any good charts?
Any good cryptos? Any good anything?
We'll take a look. You know, any good
anything? Let's take a look.
Just pop it in the chat.
Then after that, I've got to go do some
some intense landscaping work.
Do I think we'll have an alt run next
bow run? I do. I actually do.
I'm feeling it in my bones, guys, that
the the alt season is going to happen
now that everyone's out. Now that
everyone's out, people are going to feel
left behind and probably like big money
is going to start pumping them up and
and the retail is going to be left
behind. You know,
SpaceX is pumping. Let's check it out.
You know, we've been looking for a
SpaceX pump.
We've been looking for a SpaceX pump,
baby. Look at that.
Look at that. Look at that. Look at
that, man. Look, you can't just have a
falling wedge on Elon Musk and not
expect at least some kind of breakout.
[music] You know, look at that.
Do I invest in spot bitcoin right now?
Absolutely.
Uh, a
yeah, look, SpaceX, man, looking good. I
I I I told y'all I told y'all we had
some We had some deniers in the chat. We
had some SpaceX deniers in the chat.
We had some people in the chat. They
said, "Look, bro. Space is fake. It's
all water up there." I said, "Look, it's
Elon Musk, man. This thing is about to
shoot a rocket up to the moon, baby.
About to blast straight through the Van
Allen radiation belt right here." Bam.
Straight to the moon, baby. Boom. You
know what I'm saying?
All right. Uh, what else are we going to
look at? A man I have remember trading a
back in the summer of 2020 on Binance
futures.
Do you guys remember that? Do you
remember that when we used to trade
altcoins on Binance in the US with no
VPN? Do you remember that?
Well, I mean is a looking good?
Is it looking good?
Let's see here. Let's take a look at the
global volume here on on on Binance.
At least I remember trading it in the
summer 2020, but it looks like it's not
on Binance. Maybe I was trading the
Bitcoin pair. Maybe it was Maybe it was
Maybe it was the summer 2021.
No, it couldn't have been.
Huh, that's weird. Where what happened
to all A history here? I will say this
about a
we have this that we have just broken
out of that looks pretty cool falling
wedge that has been disrupted
to the downside. We've taken the
liquidity wick from October 10th
and um we've even taken these lows here.
Wow. We've even taken this low here.
This actually does look pretty nice. I'm
not going to lie. Wow.
Didn't take that low, but we did take
this low. We took this low. We took this
low.
That's That is pretty nice looking.
Let's go ahead and pull some Fibonacci.
Some Fibonacci.
Oh, would you look at that? We're
bouncing right from the altcoin pocket.
Can you even spot it? Wow. Would you
look at that? We're bouncing right from
the right from the altcoin pocket.
Yeah. Yeah. Let's take out the global
volume like once again. Let's take out
Yeah. Would be nice to get a little bit
more of a dip, but uh let's take it out
from here.
Yeah. Oh, I guess
I don't like the divergences though. But
there's definitely a change. There's
definitely a change of the character
here. There's definitely a ch. I
[snorts] mean, this is something like we
haven't seen. Look at that nice monthly
candle here. [music]
Um, wow. I mean, for the first time
since August 2025,
we have a blue candle here.
June, July.
It is looking pretty nice. We are We are
at some support.
You know, it is pretty crazy that we
topped out December 2024
and then we made a double top in August.
I mean, if we come back up to where we
were, that is a potential 300% gain.
Let's check out the risk-to-reward ratio
on this one.
You know, the monthly green dot is a
printing, baby.
It's a good risk-to-reward 9 to1.
It's a pretty good risk-to-reward. It
does look pretty good right now.
Honestly, I just don't really like the
weekly divergences.
Shout out to Akin, who's 34 today, and
he lost over 30 lbs this year. That's
amazing. Congratulations to Akin losing
34 34 lbs.
You know, that's what's up.
I made you a burger. The question is, do
I want it on lettuce cups or sourdough
bread or a bed of rice? Um,
uh, that's a good question, man.
Definitely not on a bed of rice right
now. I'm totally off the rice right now.
Like, big time. I I actually hate rice
right now. I know. I used to eat
bossmati, but not anymore. Um, let's
see. It's It's I did legs today, bro.
And I only I'm only 2,000 calories deep.
I have to eat another 3,000 calories
in four hours. [music]
So, give me the sourdough bread, man.
Give me the sourdough bread. How many
grams of sourdough bread is it? You
know, how many grams of sourdough bread
is it if we were put it on the scale?
Cuz like honestly,
sourdough bread
per 100 g is going to be about about 250
calories.
So, if it's 50 grams for each each slice
of bread, man, if you make it 100 grams
for each slice of bread,
that's 500 calories right there. That's
pretty good. I I'll take the sourdough
bread. What What percent beef is it? Is
it lean beef or is it fatty beef?
Is it lean beef [music] or is it fatty?
I want to know before I eat my patty.
About to sit back. You know it's so
splatty. Jay Casper, we got the Hattie
on the head. Trades only [music] in the
green, never in the red. Hopefully you
listen to exactly what I said. Cuz you
know if you don't, you might end up
dead. Not financial advice, but instead
you got to listen to the wisdom, [music]
the Bitcoin price, the grisom. Got the
light shining straight through the
prism. Jake [music] Casper, you know you
miss him. Got a burger from Dave
Digital. Looking like my name is B.
[music] You know I'm a permable. You
know we like to walk on the treadmill
[singing] up the hole. Yeah. My best
friend's [music] name is Bill. And now
we're walking up the big old hill. Jason
Casper, we got the drill like the flute
player. Her name [music] is Hillary.
Hillary Clinton versus Donald Trump.
Bitcoin. Are we about to dump or maybe
[music] pump? Let's take a look at the
charts. We got the blue and purple just
like a work of art. Oh man. [music]
$300 in the green. I mean in the blue.
That's what I'm seeing [music] cuz we
shorted 646 Bitcoin price back to her
old tricks.
[music]
This is an interesting beat as well.
80%. Okay. [music]
Rap about Akin being fat. I don't know
if I can.
Um,
he's down to 148 lbs. How tall is this
guy?
Everything's going to be worth two
pizzas after the bubble pop of market.
Um,
[laughter]
that's funny. Uh, yeah. Oh, the beat's
over now. Those are some good lyrics,
though, bro.
All right, let's check out gold.
Let's check out gold.
Good old XAU.
Wow,
it's looking good. Oh, yeah. I I I
honestly I'm more convinced now that
this is the bottom. So,
this is kind of like
I mean we have changed structure now on
the weekly. You know, this very well
could be the bottom. You know, we were
talking about the case that this was the
bottom and that this was the higher low
here. We were saying this is either
higher or low. What it would even be
better is we make a lower low, but we're
not guaranteed. But this is a really
nice weekly bottom. Honestly, very rare,
very bullish looking signal. And now we
have in fact the change of structure.
So, you know what that means to me is
a higher low now [music] if we're gifted
with it after a pump like this could be
very nice. So, [music] we have our last
golden pocket pull. Would be really nice
to come up to here and get a back test
and then do this. Would be really nice
right now. Go ahead and pull the
Fibonacci.
Paparazzi. Fibonacci.
Playing yatsi. Paparacei. Fibonacci.
We're playing roachi. Yatsi. Don't be a
Nazi,
you know.
Yeah, we got the Fibonacci paparachi.
We're out here [music] playing yatsi.
Don't be a Nazi. We got the Fibonacci
paparazzi. We're playing yachi. Don't be
[music and singing] a Nazi. Fibonacci
paparazzi. Don't be a Nazi. Just play
yachi.
Fibonacci paparazzi.
Don't be a Nazi. [music]
Hey yo, we got the Fibonacci. We out
here flashing cameras like we're the
paparazzi. We sit down around the table
to play yatsi. [music] We got a little
mustache, but I'm not a Nazi cuz we
pulling Fibonacci. Then we sit down, you
know, we playing yatsi outside taking
pictures, paparazzi. [music]
Got a little mustache, but I'm not a
Nazi. Hey yo, here we go. Gold [music]
pumping just like Kamala Donald Trump.
But next thing I know, we slumping
[music] cuz we trying to do it, but we
always dumping. Sit down [singing] on
the toilet. Let the muscles loose and
the brown stuff comes out the caboose.
Jay Castner must be [music] drinking
juice cuz he's here. He's letting loose.
We got the Oh, [music] that was an
abruptly ended beat right there.
Honestly,
that was an abruptly ended beat right
now. Yeah, look at that. Silver is a
better trade, you think?
All right. All right. All right, guys.
You know what? [laughter] I think this
is a good place to end the stream, man.
Ah, look, God bless you guys in Jesus
name. May the Lord bless you. May he
bless your families.
I'm I'm very thankful and grateful to
the Lord for his mercy and his grace,
his His love, his favor, his protection,
and I'm very grateful for eternal life.
Praise the [music] Lord. Hope you guys
have a wonderful weekend, and Lord
willing, I'll see you guys next week.
Peace.